Abaddon 是恶魔
Abaddon, she's a demon.
而且还是
Who turns out.
地狱骑士
Is a knight of hell.
被Lucifer亲手挑选出来的
Knights of hell are handpicked by.
地狱骑士
Lucifer himself.
- 我是你的王 - 说到这个
- I'm your king - About that.
现在 我们俩
Right now, you and I.
需要讨论一下更朝换代问题了
Are goona talk about reign change.
我怎么才能停下
How do I stop.
放手吧
Just let it go.
我们过后会想出办法
We'll figure it out.
Sam
Sam.
Sam受伤了 伤得很严重
Sammy's hurt.He's hurt real bad.
这条祈祷面向所有
This one goes out to any angels.
长耳朵的天使
With their ears on.
我是Dean Winchester
This is Dean Winchester.
我需要帮助
And I need your help.
兄弟 别急啊
Easy there, brother.
我听到你的祈祷了
I heard your prayer.
我是来帮忙的
And I am here to help.
想帮忙吗 先说你是谁
You wanna help?Start with a name.
Ezekiel
Ezekiel.
我们之前说好的
Well, we had a deal.
我拖住他们
I fight.
- 你救Sam - 还有一个办法
- You save - There's a chance I can.
救你弟弟 从他体内救
Fix your brother, from inside.
如何救
How would it work.
我养伤的同时 也在帮Sam恢复
I heal Sam while I'm healing myself.
等他康复了
And when he's healed.
我就会离开
I leave.
他会醒过来 对吧
He's gonna wake up, right.
是的
He will.
醒来以后呢 他会不会
So what he does, what, is he gonna.
感觉到你的存在 还是默默数伤口
Feel you inside?Triaging his spleen.
他不会感觉到我的存在
He will not feel me, not now.
没理由让他知道
There's no reason for him to know.
我在他体内 如果Sam不同意
I'm here at all.Without his acceptance.
他可以在任何时候排斥我
Sam can eject me, at any time.
一旦Sam排斥我
If Sam does eject me.
他就会死
He will die.
那我们现在就守住这个秘密
Then we keep it a secret for now.
所以 Cass变成人类了吗
So, what, Cass is human.
差不多
Ish.
我的意思是 他
I mean he's got.
没了荣光 没了翅膀 没了
No grace, no wings, no.
反正 什么天使技能都没了
Harp, whatever the hell else he had.
好吧
Okay.
他去哪儿了
Where did he crash land.
他从公用电话上给我打了电话
Called me from a payphone.
他当时在科罗拉多的朗蒙特市 我让他
From Longmont, Colorado.I told him just to.
- 去基地 - 你觉得他能
- Make for the bunker - You think he can.
大老远的跑去基地吗
Handle a road trip like that.
Cass也不小了
Cass is a big boy.
要是出了什么事 他知道我们的电话
Things go breaking bad, he knows our number.
现在 我在担心别的
Now I got bigger worries.
坠落的天使
The fallen angels.
对
Yeah.
多亏了Metatron 现在有好几千
I mean thanks to Metatron, we now have.
既困惑 又不稳定的核弹
A couple of thousands confused loose nukes.
在外面乱跑
Walking around down there.
你觉得他们会干什么
What do you think they're gonna do.
完全不知道
I have no damn clue.
Crowley呢 你有没有
What about Crowley?You.
我是很想
I would love nothing better than.
干掉那个老混蛋
To ice that limey bitch.
但是我又想
But then I thought to myself.
Sam Winchester会怎么做
What would Sam Winchester do.
我
I'd.
会一刀插他脑袋里
Stab him in the brain.
好吧
Oh.
然后我想到 地狱之王
Well, I figured the king of hell.
可能知道不少的事 所以为什么不
Might know a few things, so why not.
逼他说出所有事
Zero Dark Thirty his ass.
等下
Wait.
所以 Crowley
So, Crowley is.
还活着吗
Alive.
当然
Oh, yeah.
他就是我后备箱里的垃圾
He'a a junk in my trunk.
搞什么
What the hell.
是Dean吗
Dean.
你活着回来了
You're here alive.
嗯 因为你瞄得太准
Yeah.'Cause you are a crappy shot.
跟 饥饿游戏 女主一样准
Katniss.
抱歉
Sorry.
最近几天真是糟透了
It's been a bad couple of days.
我睡不着 吃不下
I haven't slept.I haven't eaten, and.
上厕所都很痛苦
I've pretty backed-up.
好吧 你说太多了
Okay, you overshare.
上次跟你打过电话以后 这地方就完全失控了
After we talked, this place went nuts.
各种警报全在响
All right, there're some alarm on and.
所有机械设备都疯了一样
The machines are freaking out and.
这间房子又自己锁上了
The bunker just locked down.
我还打不开门 我的手机又不能用了
I couldn't open the door myself.My cellphone stopped working.
我还以为世界末日了
I thought the world's ending.
差不多
Close.
天使都坠落了
The angels' fell.
什么意思
What does that mean.
情况很不好
Nothing good.
听着 下次再有世界末日
Listen, next time the world's ending.
最好拿上枪
Grab a gun.
我手机有信号
I got service.
又好了
It's back online.
可能是你从外面开门的时候
Maybe when you open the door from.
系统重启了
The outside door reset the system.
嗯 这样最好
Yeah, okay.Let's go with that.
都好吗
Hey, all good.
什么时候好过 走
Is it ever.Come on.
不是吧
No.
你们好
Hello.
永远都不会烦
Never get tired doing that.
真有家的感觉
Homey.
你们从哪儿找到这么漂亮的地方的
Where did you get this fantasitic little tree house.
好了 现在是这样
All right.Here's how this gonna go.
你给我们地球上每一个恶魔的名字
You're gonna give us the name of demon on earth.
还有被附身者的名字
And the people they're possessing.
是吗
Am I.
不像我会干的事
Doesn't sound like me.
我看到你崩溃后的样子 Crowley
I saw you break down, Crowley.
就在我想治愈你的时候
When I was trying to cure you.
我知道你心里某处又回归了人性 也许
I know a part of you was human again, maybe.
- 现在还在 我还知道 - 他她它 说完了
- Still lives.I also know - Bla bla boo.Done.
我很清楚的是
Good.Cause this is what I know.
我不会告诉你们任何事
I'm not giving you anything.
我为什么要说
Why would I.
你们又没有谈条件的筹码
You have no leverage, darlings.
你们一不会关了地狱的大门
You're not gonna close the gate of hell.
因为你们之前有过机会
Because you didn't.
二不会杀了我 因为我还活着
You're not gonna kill me because you haven't.
请问还有什么可谈的
So what's left.
我们倒是有些想法
We have a few ideas.
酷刑吗 真棒
Torture.Brilliant.
我真等不及看Sam穿上高跟鞋
Can't wait to see Sam in stilettos.
和女士紧身衣
And a lether bustier.
真正和Sam来场性虐
Really putting the S-A-M into S and M.
说实话
Honestly boys.
你们还能拿我怎么办
What are you gonna do to me.
我本来就什么都试过了
That I don't do to myself just for kicks.
每周五晚
Every Friday night.
祝你幸福
Have fun.
Crowley在这儿干什么
What's Crowley doing here.
他怎么还没死 你为什么还没一刀捅死他
Why isn't he dead.Why haven't you stabbed him right now.
淡定 Kevin 我们需要他
Chill out, Kevin, okay, we need him.
什么
What.
Kevin 是这样的
Kevin, look.
如果我们能让Crowley直接告诉我们
If we can get Crowley to give us the.
主要恶魔的名字
Name of demon he's got topside.
我们就能干掉
We can hunt them down.
所有恶魔
All of them.
他会开口的
He'll break.
等他告诉我们全部之后
Okay?When he does.
我们抓着他 你来动手杀他
We'll hold him down while you knife him.
然后我们就能吃着冰淇淋看脱衣舞了
Then we'll all go up for ice-cream and strippers.
离他远点儿好吗
Just stay away from him, all right.
现在怎么办
So now what.
我去打几个电话
I gonna make some phone calls.
你继续看天使预言板
You need to hit the Angel Tablets.
看能不能找到Metatron
See if you could find anything on the spell.
用来清扫天堂的咒语
That Metatron used to empty out Heaven.
说不定咱们能在
And maybe we could reverse.
天使们惹大麻烦之前扭转局面
Before the God's squad does too much damage.
前提是我们有够幸运
And if we are lucky.
现在 开始留心任何跟天使有关的事件
All right, checking out anything for angely.
或者恶魔的
Or demony.
或者妖魔鬼怪的 或者
Or monstery or ghosty or.
今年可真有够忙的
It's gonna be a busy year.
我是Abaddon
My name is Abaddon.
我就不多介绍了 咱们来聊聊你们
But enough about me.Let's talk you.
Jason告诉我 你们是一群暴力
Jason tells me that you're all violent.
唯利是图的投机主义者
Power-hungry opportunist.
那么现在谁来告诉我
So maybe you can tell me.
地狱到底他妈的发什么了什么
What the hell happened to Hell.
还有恶魔 我说
And demons, I mean.
你就管这个破玩意儿叫肉身吗
You call that a meatsuit.
去年我接手了72宗交易
I closed 72 deals last year.
小孩儿都喜欢老奶奶
Kids love grandma.
这就是问题所在
And that's the problem.
交易
Deals.
我们居然在交易
We're paying.
而不是掠夺
For what we should be taking.
是谁让Crowley当老大的
Who put Crowley in charge.
怎么不说话
What's the matter.
舌头都被地狱恶犬吃了是吗
Hellhound got your tongue.
你们居然听取他的命令
You took orders from him.
他是地狱之王
He's the King.
他只是个商人
He's a salesman.
真正的王应该征战
A king fights.
应该降伏四方
A king conquers.
而不是傻兮兮的坐在那儿
A king does more than sit around.
读什么交易契约
Reading contracts.
但是现在 王死了
But the King's dead.
女王回来了
Long live the Queen.
我可以训练你们
I can train you.
给你们新的肉身
I can get you new bodies.
然后一起进军地狱
And we'll march into Hell.
被拥戴为解放地狱的革命者
Where we'll be greeted as liberators.
恶魔就此崛起 扫荡全世界
And demonskind will rise up and sweep over the earth.
所有的人类 和坠落的天使
And all the humans and all the angels.
都要臣服于我
With their clipped wings will bow to me.
不然 就要死
Or they'll burn.
那Crowley怎么办
What about Crowley.
Crowley已经死了
Crowley's dead.
无意冒犯 亲爱的
Well, no offense, honey.
但是我们都以为你死了
But we all thought you were dead until like.
也一周前的事
A week ago.
如果Crowley回来了怎么办
And what if Crowley does come back.
听着 很多人
Look, a lot of us.
以前惧怕他 现在也一样
We were scared of him, a lot of us still are.
证明Crowley再也不会回来
Prove that Crowley's really gone.
也许你的小计划就能奏效
And then maybe the scheme of yours will work.
也许不能
Or not.
说实话
Honestly.
我一直觉得你们几个骑士都被评价过高了
I always thought you Knights were overrated.
去地狱
You go to Hell.
告诉他们
And you tell them.
我来了
I'm coming.
没错 掉进人间的天使
Yeah, Irv.fallen angels.
还真是问题
Well, that's a wrinkle.
相信我
Well, trust me.
他们就是一群衣冠禽兽
They're just monsters With good PR.
如果你撞上了一个
So, if you run into one.
扔进圣油里炸
Torch his ass with the holy oil.
哦对了 如果他掉了把 银质的剑
Oh, and if they drop a, like a silver sword.
千万抢过来
Grab it.
那东西很好用
Those pig stickers come in handy.
没问题
Okay, criminy.
我知道这听起来挺奇怪的
And look I know this is weird.
奇怪什么 我们每天都跟奇怪打交道
Hell, Deano, weird is what we do.
还记得那个在萨斯卡通市
I remember this case me and Bobby.
我和Bobby一起遇到的那次
We worked in Saskatoon and this.
狼人连体双胞胎
Werewolf siamese twins.
谁告诉你的
Who told you about that.
每次他喝高了都会讲一遍
Every time he drunk Labatt's.
如果碰上任何麻烦 打给我们
So if you run into any troubles, give us a call.
对了 散播这个消息
Okay, and…spread the word.
越多猎人知道越好
The more hunters know the better.
没问题
Okay, Roger Dodger.
这是你第一次去市里过周末对吧
So it's your first weekend to pass into town right.
我都安排好了
So I set it all up.
Jim会在酒吧等着 他喜欢
Jim's waiting at the bar and has a thing.
穿着制服的
For man in uniform.
你就不停买酒就好
So, you just start buying shots.
到早上再谢我
Then you can thank me in the morning.
酷
Cool.
现在
Now, that.
才像话
Is more like it.
需要帮助吗
Need some help.
是的 我也不懂
Yeah, I don't know.
好像有什么部件坏了
I think the thingy broke.
也许我可以载你一程
I could give you a lift into town.
太好了
That would be amazing.
谢谢了
Thanks.
干得漂亮
Nice hunting.
天呐
Oh my god.
这儿就像被硫磺腌过一样
This place reeks of sulfur.
臭气熏天 还有不正常的雷暴
Stink, the freak thunder storm.
三公里之内的牛都死光了
Every cow dead within three miles.
赌1000美元 绝对是恶魔
I'll take demons for 1000, Alex.
Stark特工 和Banner特工 FBI
Hi, Agent Stark and Banner.FBI.
我们要调查一下
Just need to have a look around.
为什么
Why.
这是军事案件
This is a military case.
不关政府的事儿
Not a federal one.
我们的顶头上司可不是这么说的
No, it's not what our supervisor said.
是吗
That so.
那我或许该跟他谈一谈
Then maybe him and I are to have a chat.
好吧
Okay.
嘿
Hey.
嘿 头儿 有点儿小麻烦
Hey, boss, we've got a little problems here.
谁是头儿
Boss.
当地军方
Yeah, just local badge.
要求出示相关证明
Needs confirmation we're supposed to be here.
证明是从华盛顿FBI
How the the word came down from a.
直派的口令
FBI headquarters in DC.
等等 什么
Wait, what, what.
好的
Yeah.
我是Miranda中士
This is Sergeant Miranda Bates.
请问你是
Who am I talking to.
Kevin
Kevin.
姓Solo
Solo.
你多大了
How old are you.
足够大了
Old enough.
我是FBI的人
And I'm with the FBI.
你最好照我们说的做
See you have to do what I say or.
听着 我不会做任何事
Listen, kid.I don't have to do anything.
也不会从小孩儿那接受命令
And I don't take orders from the feeb.
你最好赶紧给我解释清楚
So unless you could me one good reason.
为什么会有两个漂亮脸蛋探员
You got a couple of pretty boy agents.
在我负责的犯罪现场乱跑
Poking around my crime scene.
要不然我就立刻逮捕他们
I'm gonna put them in cuffs and.
再揍你一顿 明白了吗
Spank your ass raw.You understand.
去年 卡博市
Cabo, last year.
什么
What.
这就是我的解释
That's my reason.
我最喜欢的是你戴着宽边帽
My favourite's is you wearing sombrero.
和一个诡异的面具 跟一个裸男
And doing a body shot off some naked guy.
贴在一起
In a Luchador mask.
还真是有看点
Super classy.
你怎么知道的
How do you find that.
因为我是Kevin Solo
Cause I'm Kevin freaking solo.
除非你想这件事儿闹到
So, unless you want to this forwarded.
你的直属上司 Velasquez少校那里
To your commanding officer Major Velasquez.
我劝你最好 按我的人说的话做
I suggest you give my guys anything they want.
明白了吗
Understand.
是
Yes.
是 长官
Yes, sir.
Kevin
Kevin.
你是怎么办到的
What the hell did you just do.
他们的电脑都连的是一个网
All military computers are linked to the same network.
然后呢
And.
我黑进去了
I hacked it.
Kevin
Hey, Kevin.
干得不错 伙计
Good job, buddy.
有什么发现吗
Hey, anything.
这个人胸口有个弹孔
Yes, this guys was shot in the heart.
致命伤吗
That what killed him.
有可能
Maybe.
15 20年之前的事了
They've been 15, 20 years ago.
这儿的每个人身上都有一处致命伤
Everyone on this bodies has a fatal wound.
两处 或者三处
Or two, or three.
但是时间都很久
But they're all old.
所以我们看到的只是肉身
So we're looking at meatsuits.
就算是肉体受伤了
Bodies took a lickin and.
里面的恶魔还是活蹦乱跳
Demons inside kept'em ticking.
有可能
Probably.
我觉得他们被附身了
I think they were possessed.
现在那些士兵也一样
Now those soldiers are.
嘿
Hey.
打扰一下 探员
Excuse me, agents.
我们拿到了一台监控摄像机的录影带
We pulled this off a security camera.
你们需要看一下吗
You might wanna take a look.
Abaddon吗
Abaddon.
没开玩笑吧
Seriously.
我以为你烧掉那具肉身了
I thought you Kentucky fried that meatsuit.
我烧了 Dean
I did, Dean.
那她是怎么回来的
Well, how did she get it back.
谢谢
Thank you.
她怎么又追上大兵了
And why's she playing G.I.Joe.
毫无头绪
No clue.
不如等找到她的时候 你自己去问她
Why don't you ask her when we find her.
我会的 然后我会砍下她该死的脑袋
Oh I will, and I'm gonna chop her freaking head off.
再一次
Again.
好了 Pete
All right, Pete.
Winchester俩兄弟在哪儿
The Winchesters, where are they.
去死吧
Bite me.
我问你Winchester兄弟俩在哪儿
I said where the Winchesters.
我说你去死吧 小平头
And I said bite me, crew cut.
让我来告诉你们该怎么做吧 小伙子们
Let me show you how it's done, boys.
救我
Help me.
救命啊
Help.
随便你怎么尖叫
You can scream all you want to.
没人会听到的
No one's gonna hear you.
现在我们来聊聊Sam和Dean
Now let's talk Sam and Dean.
你好
Hello.
这是Dean的电话
This is Dean's number.
但你不是他 你是谁
But you are not a Winchester, who are you.
我谁都不是
I'm nobody.
好吧 陌生人
Well, nobody.
我需要你给那俩兄弟带个话
I need you to give those boys a message for me.
我手上有他们可能想要的东西
I have something they might want.
Kevin 等等 慢点说
Kevin, wait, wait, slow down.
她给了我一个坐标 44 053051 123 12786028
She gave me this coordinate, 44.053051by - 123.12786088.
还有两个名字 Irv Franklin和Tracy Bell
And two names, Irv Franklin and Tracy Bell.
Irv是我们的朋友 不知道Tracy是谁
Irv is a friend, don't know Tracy.
那个女的说他们都是猎人
The lady said they were hunters.
如果你不去救他们 她就会杀了他们
And if you didn't go save them, that she would kill them.
这话我以前听过
I've heard that song before.
Dean 她是谁
Dean, who was she.
她是个坏人
She's the bad guy.
好了 新任务
Well, new job.
去翻看学者们所有关于地狱骑士的记录
Dig up everything men of letters have on Knights of Hell.
地狱骑士吗
Knights of hell.
好
Sure.
找一个能杀掉他们的方法
You find a way to kill one.
我说的是 永远死去的方法
I mean permanently.
好好查
Drop a dime.
谢谢你 Kevin
Thanks, Kevin.
那个坐标指向俄勒冈州的尤金市
That numbers point to a spot on the outskirts of Eugene, Oregon.
你知道这是个陷阱吧
You know this is a trap, right.
嗯
Yep.
那我们还这样自己掉进去吗
And we just gonna walk right into it.
迫不及待
Guns blazing.
你会和我一起吗
You with me.
你知道答案的
You know it.
你就是第三项试炼
You are the third trial, Crowley.
我现在开始吗
Do I start.
你被我们困住了
You're our bitch.
能被原谅吗
To even looking for forgiveness.
你这个恶魔马上就要变成凡人了
Your demon ass is going to be a mortal ass.
这些对你来说都毫无意义吗
None of this means anything to you.
她需要爱
She needs to be loved.
她值得被爱
She deserves it.
我值得被爱
I deserve to be loved.
我只是想要被爱
I just want to be loved.
Kevin
Kevin.
Kevin我知道是你
Kevin, I know it's you.
我在哪里都能分辨出你小脚丫的脚步声
I recognize the pitter-patter of your little feet anywhere.
对 逃避 你只会这么做
That's right, run, that's what you do.
我能理解 真的
I understand.I do.
你是 那个词怎么说 软弱
You are, what's the word?Weak.
你好啊 Kev
Hi ya, Kev.
这发生什么了
What the hell happen here.
几年前这里的化工厂发生了泄漏事故
Local chemical plant sprung a leak years ago.
他们疏散了方圆几公里内的街区
They have evacuated three squares of blocks.
我猜污染应该还在
I guess it's still contaminated.
整个地方都被污染了吗
This whole place is poisoned.
是的
Yeah.
没用的
That's not gonna help.
做点防护措施没坏处
It doesn't hurt.
Dean
Dean.
Irv
Irv.
Abaddon在哪
Where's Abaddon.
Abaddon一直在折磨猎人们
Abaddon' s been torturing hunters.
她在打听你们的消息
She tried to get an intel on you boys.
你知道为什么吗
Do you know why.
我觉得 她不是想给你们
I serious doubt, she wants to add you.
寄圣诞贺卡
To her Christmas card list.
你们到底要不要救我们
Now do you want to make with the rescue or what.
等我们用圣水试一下你
Right after you take a shot of holy water.
满意了
Happy.
抱歉
Sorry about that.
没关系
Don't worry about it.
你们不会想看到我们变成黑眼恶魔的
Last thing you need is us popping black eyes.
Tracy 是吗
Tracy, right.
我是Sam Winchester
I'm the Sam Winchester.
很好
Good for you.
她是新人 我们在萨克拉门多一起工作过
She's new, We did shifter job in Sacramento together.
很聪明 但是有点多话
Smart, but got a mouth on her.
我们准备一下吧
Let's gear up.
什么风把你吹来我的闺房了 帅哥
So, what brings you to my boudoir, handsome.
你得告诉我怎么杀掉地狱骑士
You need to tell me how to kill a Knight of Hell.
Abaddon给你们添麻烦了吧
Abaddon giveing you trouble, right.
告诉你 你放我走
Tell you what, you let me go.
我会亲手帮你收拾那个小贱人
And I'll spit roast the little whore for you.
听起来不错吧
Sound good.
你在骗人
You're bluffing.
你不知道怎么做
You don't know.
我知道的很多
Oh, I know plenty.
比如 我知道她爱你
For example, I know she'd love you.
又瘦弱又听话 正合她的胃口
Skinny, submissive.You're just here type.
闭嘴
Shut up.
好吧
Fine.
这不是你来找我的真正原因
That's not what you came for anyway, no really.
你在想什么Kevin
What's on you mind, Kevin.
你可以告诉我 我们是朋友
You can tell me, we are friends.
你折磨过我
You tortured me.
我折磨我的所有朋友
I tortured all my friends.
这就是我展现爱意的方式
That's how I show love.
我在一个不正常的家庭环境中长大
I was raised in a dysfunctional home environment.
你杀了我的妈妈
You killed my mom.
我有吗
Did I.
我是说你能肯定吗
I mean are you sure.
你见过她的尸体吗
Did you ever see a body.
你是怎么确信她就死了呢
I mean how could you be sure she's dead.
你的能力不止这样 小家伙
You can do better than that, little man.
这就对了
That's right.
发泄出来吧
Let it all out.
好吧 我们有圣水
All right we got Jesus juice.
枪 填满刻着恶魔陷阱的子弹
Gun loaded with devil's trap bullets.
给恶魔一枪 就能困住它们
Shoot a demon, put them on lockdown.
天使之刃很有用
Angle blade works.
他们来了
They're coming.
很好
Good.
他们带了来福枪
They've got assault rifles.
好吧 我们走
Okay, let's go.
有什么计划吗
So, what's the play.
过来抓我们啊 混蛋
Come and get it, you dicks.
趴下
Down now.
过来抓我们啊 混蛋
Come and get it, you dicks.
混蛋
Damn it.
好吧 我们现在要拿出海豹突击队的阵势
Alright, We got to flank SEAL team douche in there, so.
Irv 你和我从左边走
Lrv, you and me go left.
Sam和Tracy从右边走
Sam and Tracy go right.
好吧
Okay.
我们走吧
Let's move.
别碰我
Don't touch me.
有什么问题吗
What's problem.
我的家人都是因为他死的
My family's dead because of him.
什么
What.
我看着一个恶魔
I watched a demon.
屠杀我的父母 与此同时
Slaughter my parents, and the whole time.
它谈论着它要如何庆祝
It talked about how it was celebrating.
一个蠢货把Lucifer放出了牢笼
How some dumb kid let Lucifer out of his cage.
好了 我们得行动了
Okay, alright, we got to move.
这个女孩跟着我
Girl is with me.
Irv
Irv.
好吧 我们走吧 孩子
Okay, let's go, son.
那么
There.
现在你感觉到你的感受了
Now that you've felt your feels.
也许我们能谈谈
Maybe we can talk.
不
No.
让我简单点说 Kevin
I'm gonna make this simple, Kevin.
让我走
Let me go.
我会把你妈妈还给你
And I'll give you back your mother.
她死了
She's dead.
哦 她想得美
Oh, she wishes she was.
在经历过这么多苦痛之后
After what I had my heavies do to her.
她求着我让她去死
She's begging for it.
但是你知道 我是不会
But when have you ever known me.
让任何人轻易逃脱的
To let anyone off easy.
你以为Sam和Dean在乎她
You think Sam and Dean care about her.
你以为他们在乎你
You think they care about you.
你只是在这满足他们的需要
You are just here to serve their needs.
只是如此
Nothing more.
你总有一天会失去一切 Kevin
You're gonna lose, Kevin.
失去一切
Everything.
这只是时间问题
It's just a matter of time.
当Winchester们利用完你之后
When the Winchesters are done with you.
他们会毫不犹豫的把你扔到一边
They'll toss you aside without a second thought.
因为他们可以
Because they can.
因为他们认为自己是特别的
Because they think they are special.
而且
And because, well.
总有下一个先知可以任他们使唤
There's always another prophet waiting in the wings.
虽然我才是身披镣铐的那个
I'm the one in chains.
但在这儿 你我都是囚犯
But we are both prisoners here.
你让我走 怎么样
What say you let me go.
我们一起走出这些门
We walk out those doors together.
我们一起赢 怎么样
What say we both win.
好吧 我想他们还在里面
Okay I think they are still inside.
我们等着他们出来
We wait till they come out.
然后一个一个打到他们
And we pick them off one by one.
听着 为保准起见
Listen, for the record.
Sam不是唯一一个认为自己做了正确的事
Sam's not the only guy who thought he is doing right.
但却眼睁睁看着灾难来临的人
And watched it all go to crap.
好吗 这只是
Okay, it's just part of being.
做为猎人的一部分
Being a hunter.
是作为人的一部分
Being human.
如果你想对Sam生气
Look, you want to be pissed off at Sam.
这没什么 我理解
That's fine, I get it.
但如果你想向谁寻仇
But if you want to go after somebody.
你得确保那是个黑眼恶魔
You make sure they got black eyes.
你得知道什么才是
Got to know what the real monsters.
真正的邪恶 孩子
Are in this world, kid.
Sam 你还好吧
Sam, you copacetic.
还好
Yeah.
很好
Good.
把你的家伙给我
Now hand me that toothpick.
你 Dean和Tracy赶紧离开这儿
And you and Dean and Tracy beat feet out of here.
什么
What.
我一个人进去
I'm going in there alone.
为你们争取尽可能多的时间
And buy you as long time as I can.
Irv 这等同于自杀
Irv, that's death.
是的
Yeah, well.
那是我自找的
It's what I got coming.
这是我的错 Sam
It's my fault Sam.
当时
I was.
我正泡在酒馆里 有了个艳遇
In some dive, sloppy, and I met some girl.
等我再次清醒过来 我就被困在了一张床里
The next thing you know.I'm trapped to some bed.
她用尽方法
And she's twisting things.
折磨我
That ain't supposed to be twisted.
她是谁
She who.
Abaddon
Abaddon.
我交出了他们
I gave them up.
Pete Tracy 我交出了他们所有人
Pete, Tracy, I gave them all up.
所以你给我那把刀
So you hand me that blade.
让我做我必须做的事
And you let me do what I got to do.
帮我
So help me.
你们俩合作还挺愉快的嘛
Nice grouping.
防弹衣
Kevlar.
比附魔子弹强
Beat magic bullet.
我爱高科技
I love the future.
听着 我的车在三个街区之外
Listen, my car is three blocks over.
去拿些子弹 拿些圣水
Go get more bullets, more holy water.
能拿什么拿什么
Get everything.
等等 那你呢
Wait, what about you.
快走 快走 现在
Just go, go now.
终于就剩我们俩了
Alone at last.
我很想你
I missed you.
你想我了吗
Did you miss me.
太好了 我没错过最精彩的部分
Cool, I didn't miss the best part.
真高兴你们在我打完电话之后就赶来了
So appreciate you boys coming when I call.
这就是为什么我这么喜欢你们Winchester
I think it's what I like most about you Winchesters.
总是那么听话
You're so obedience.
带着自我毁灭式的愚蠢
And suicidally stupid.
我喜欢这一点
I like that, too.
你是想跟我打一架还是滚床单
Are we gonna fight or make out.
因为我真的有点儿搞不清楚了
Cause I'm getting some real mixed signals here.
我要Crowley
I want Crowley.
或是他的残骸
Or what's left of him.
是吗 那对我有什么好处
Yeah.What's in it for me.
我可以让你死
I let you die.
你给我Crowley的首级
You give me Crowley's head.
我就又快又干脆地扭断你的脖子
And I will snip your neck quick and clean.
你都不会感觉到什么 相信我
You won't feel a thing, trust me.
那如果我告诉你一边去呢
And if I tell you to get bent.
哦 这个
Oh, well.
知道吗
You know.
自从我第一眼见到 我就一直很爱你的身体
I've loved this body since the moment I first saw it.
你是个完美的皮囊 Dean
You are the perfect vessel, Dean.
集女孩子所有肮脏的小想法于一身
You give a girl all sorts of nasty ideas.
所以随便你怎么装作很难搞
So go ahead and play hard to get.
我会弄下这个防恶魔纹身
And I'll peel off this No-demon-allowed tattoo.
然后化成黑烟钻进你的身体
And blow smoke up your ass.
我得告诉你
I got to tell you.
咱们两个
Between you and me.
只能是个恐怖片
It is a horror show out there.
比恐怖片更糟
It can get worse.
相信我
Trust me.
一旦我进入你的身体 我会让你看着全过程
Cause once I'm on top, I'll make you watch.
而且我会用你的身体
And I'll use your body.
你知道婴儿的血液
Have you ever felt an infant's blood.
流过下巴时的感受吗
Drip down your chin.
或者在你撕碎一个女孩的肠子的时候
Or listen to a girl scream.
听着她尖叫
As you rip her guts.
你会亲自体验到的
Because you will.
你和我 亲爱的
You and me, lover.
我们会有很多时间
We'll have a grand old time.
你知道
You know.
我以为你们Winchester都很厉害呢
I thought you Winchesters are supposed to be tough.
一个天使
An angel.
怎么 你以为我们会没带帮手
What, you think we'd roll up to this mouse trap.
就闯进这个陷阱
Without some backups.
他们差点儿就杀了他 Dean
They were going to kill him, Dean.
Ezekiel
Ezekiel.
你干了什么
What the hell did you do.
我在保护你弟弟
I was protecting your brother.
我以为这是你想要的
I thought that's what you wanted.
是啊 是的 是啊 我知道
Yeah, right.yeah, I know.
我 抱歉我还在适应这件事
I…Sorry I'm still getting used to this whole thing.
我也是
As am I.
但是Sam没事吧
But Sam is okay.
他被打昏过去了
He's knocked unconscious.
在某种程度上 他还没清醒过来
In a way, he still is.
Sam一点也不会记得这些事
Sam will not remember any of this.
他醒过来之后
So what the hell am I supposed to tell him.
我要怎么跟他解释
When he comes to.
所以我刚才用了匕首
Because that's why I used the knife.
对
Right.
聪明
Smart.
可你还是很不安
You are troubled still.
是的 其实
Yes, it's just.
我知道这怪我
I know this is on me.
是我跟Sam说
I was the one who talked to Sam.
放弃关上地狱之门的
Out of boarding up hell.
所以恶魔的每个交易
'Kay?So, every demon deal.
杀的每个人
Every kill that they make.
你面前就站的是罪魁祸首
You're looking at the person who let it happen.
你在保护你的弟弟
You're protecting your brother.
我能进入Sam的思想
I'm in Sam's head.
他知道的每件事 我都知道
Everything he knows, I know.
我知道你所作的一切
And I know that what you did.
都是出于兄弟情谊
You did out of love.
是啊 听着 Zeke
Yep, look, Zeke.
我就叫你Zeke了
I'm gonna call you Zeke.
我不是那种会说
I'm not really with the whole.
什么爱啊
Love and.
- 情啊之类的 - 这就是我答应的原因
- Love - But it is the why I said yes.
对 如果连这都出问题
Yeah, and if that goes sideways.
那也是怪我
That's on me, too.
但这不会发生的
That's not going to happen.
这一切太疯狂了
This is nuts.
我是说 你是Sam
I mean you're Sam.
但你又不是Sam
But you're not Sam.
平时都是我跟他说
And normally he's the one I'm taking to.
这些话的
About all this stuff.
我信任你 Zeke
I'm trusting you, Zeke.
我只希望
I just got to hope that.
你是个好人
You are one of those good guys.
我是
I am.
但是估计坏人也会这么说
But I suppose that is what a bad guy would say.
Dean Winchester 你所作的事是正确的
Dean Winchester, you are doing the right thing.
Sam Sammy
Sam, Sammy.
Dean 发生了什么
Dean, what the hell happened.
你被人打昏倒
You took a shot to your head.
我进来救了你 跟平时一样
And I came in and saved your ass, like usual.
你单挑了三个恶魔吗
You killed three demons alone.
我这是出其不备
I took them by surprise.
有点混乱 但是运气不错
Got a little messy, I get a little lucky.
还有
And.
因为我太厉害了
I'm awesome, so there's that.
- 天哪 - 是的
- Geez - Yeah.
厉害已经不能形容你了
You're pretty damn awesome.
嘿
Hey.
你还好吗
You okay.
还好 你呢
Yeah, you.
- 一般一般 - 那就好
- More or less, yeah - Good.
我都搞定了 但是
I got everything but.
看来我来晚了
Guess I'm late to the party.
算你走运
Lucky you.
赶紧离开这个破地方
Let's blow this toxic waste dump.
我带你们去吃顿好饭 洗个舒服澡
Burges and silkwood showers on me.
Kevin
Kevin.
谁干的
Who worked you over.
Martin Hayward
Martin Hayward.
和Brandon Favors
And Brandon Favors.
他们把你弄成这样的吗
They did this to you.
不 是附他们身的恶魔干的
No, the demons.
你们问我名字 我就告诉你名字
You ask for names and I'm giving you names.
他们最近很得宠
They under underperformers.
把他们干掉 就算是帮我了
Spike them you're doing me a favor.
哇 让你开口还真是容易
Wow, you break easy.
不
Please.
要说是你那倒霉计划
You little plan to have me stew.
把我一个人扔下什么的起作用了
In my own delicious juicies.
那就真是可笑了
Pathetic.
你要名字
You want intel.
我也有要求
I want things do.
或许我们可以某些程度上达成一致
Maybe we can come to some kind of arrangement.
礼尚往来
Quid pro quo, gentlemen.
那这又算什么 赠品吗
So these are what then.Freebies.
不是
Not at all.
就当是Kevin
You can consider them fair trade.
娱乐我的回报吧
For the enjoyment that Kevin gave me.
你什么意思
What the hell is that suppose to mean.
他是我的新宠
He's my new favourite toy.
玩儿过他
Wind him up.
再看着他离开
Watch him go.
你去查那两个恶魔 我来找Kevin
You check the names.I'll find the kid.
想去哪儿啊
Where do you think you're going.
跟我说说
Talk to me.
你不能把我关在这儿
You can't keep me locked in here.
我要走
I'm leaving.
怎么可能
Like hell.
我们告诉过你不要和Crowley讲话
Man we told you not to talk to Crowley, okay.
他会搅乱你的思维
He messes with your head.
他说 我妈妈还活着
He says my mom's alive.
Crowley说如果我放了他
Crowley said if I let him go.
我妈妈就能回到我身边
He'd give her back to me.
你就相信他了
And you believe him.
他还被关在那儿 不是吗
He's still in there, isn't he.
Crowley在说谎
Crowley's lying.
如果他没有呢
And if he's not.
好吧 如果她还活着
Well, if she is alive.
她也没命了
Then she's dead.
不管怎样 她已经死了 Kevin 节哀
In every way that matters.She's dead, Kevin.I'm sorry.
我知道你想出去找她
I know you're dying to bolt, man.
我能理解
I get it.
但是 门外 是恶魔
But out that door.It's demons.
和天使 他们都非常想
And angels.And they would all love.
抓到先知
To get their hands on a prophet.
所以即使Crowley在这里
So even with Crowley's here.
这儿仍然是最安全的地方
It's still the safest place for you.
最安全的
It just is.
而且我们需要你
And we need you, man.
因为我还有用
Cause I'm useful.
因为你是我们的家人
Because you're a family.
在经历了这样那样的挫折之后
After all the crap we've been through.
在你为我们付出如此多之后
After all the good you've done.
如果你不相信我们会为你去死
Man if you don't think we'll die for you.
我都不知道该怎么说了
I don't know what to tell you.
因为你 我 Sam和Cass
Because you, me, Sam and Cass.
我们只剩彼此
We're all we've got.
但是如果 你觉得这一切都不重要
But hey, if none of that matters to you.
我不会阻拦你
I won't stop you.
Kevin在某个空房间里睡死过去了
Kevin's passed in one of the back rooms.
孩子挺坚强的
He's a tough kid.
他会挺过来的
He'll bounce back.
你又是怎么了
What's up with you.
没事
Nothing.
就是
It's just.
Tracy说我的话
What Tracy said about me.
她说的没错
She wasn't wrong.
Sam 听我说
Sam, listen to me.
你拯救的人远多于
You've helped a hell lot of people.
你伤害的人
Than you've hurt.
而且那些
So all of that.
已经是过去了
There was then, okay.
敬现在的时光
Here's to know.
你准备好了吗
So you ready for it.
坠落的天使 Abaddon
Fallen angels, Abaddon.
失去荣光的Cass 地下室里的Crowley
Cass losing his halo, Crowley in our basement.
我们就像生活在情景喜剧里一样
Crap, we're living in a freakin' sitcom.
你怎么样 你
What about you?How is the.
还好吗
The engine running.
说实在的 我现在感觉比以前
Honestly, I feel better than I have.
好多了
In a long time.
我知道外面现在很乱
I mean I realize it's crazy out there.
还有数不尽的麻烦
And we have trouble coming for us.
但是我看到身边都是
But I look around I see.
家人 朋友
Friends and family.
我很享受现在的生活
I'm happy with my life.
第一次
For the first time in.
这么久以来的第一次
Forever.
我真的这样想
I am, I really am.
就是现在
It's just things are.
一切都很好
Things are good.
再也没有比这更好的了
Never better.